{"data":[{"question":"The Louisiana Territory, an area ________ the size of France, was bought by the United States from France for 15,000,000 in 1803.","a":"than more four times","b":"more than four times","c":"four times than more","d":"is four times more than","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Despite claims that filters and low-tar tobacco make smoking somewhat safer, in fact they only marginally reduce, ________ eliminate the hazards.","a":"none","b":"no","c":"not","d":"nor","answer":"3","explain":"\n- No goes with nouns.\n- Not goes with verbs.\u00a0\n- None of + noun.\u00a0\n- Nor: used after a negative statement in order to introduce another negative statement containing a similar kind of information.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"________ many of the designs for the new capital were considered lost forever, Benjamin Banneker helped reproduce the original plans.","a":"When","b":"During","c":"If as","d":"How","answer":"1","explain":"\n- When: at or during the time that something happens.\n+ When + Clause; During + period.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Few natural elements exist in ________ that they are rarely seen in their natural environments.","a":"such small quantities","b":"so small quantities","c":"very small quantities","d":"small quantity","answer":"1","explain":"\n- So\/such...that: used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is.\u00a0\n- Such + Noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0\n- So + adj.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Generally speaking, every person ________ the potential to be a teacher, to some extent.","a":"has","b":"to have","c":"having","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- S (every person) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"________ business, a merger is a combination of two or more corporations under one management.","a":"The","b":"At","c":"On","d":"In","answer":"4","explain":"- We use In business","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"________ of commodities by air began in the 1920s at the same time as airmail service.","a":"The shipping","b":"A ship","c":"The shipped","d":"To ship","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The + definite noun.\u00a0\n- Shipping: the delivery of goods, especially by ship.\u00a0\n- Ship: used to deliver good.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Jan Malzeliger's invention, the shoe-lasting machine, ________ production but it also cut the cost of shoe production by half.","a":"not only increased","b":"not increased only","c":"increased only","d":"only have increased","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Not only...but also...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"It can sometimes ________ a home.","a":"to take months to sell","b":"take several months to sell","c":"selling takes several months","d":"to sell taking several months","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Can + Infinitive (without \"to\").","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Jellyfish are probably ________ on Earth.","a":"most numerous predators","b":"the most numerous predators","c":"most numerous of predators","d":"the most predators","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Superlative form of adjective\/adverb: \n+ Short adj: The + adj\/adv +est.\u00a0\n+ Long adj: The + most + adj\/adv.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}